Register of the Yudenich Collection, 1919-1921
Hoover Institution Archives
- ARKHIV SEVERO-ZAPODNAGO FRONTA GRAZHDANSKOI VOINY V ROSSII 1919 I 1920 GODOV
  - File 53. Reports re military situation on the Northern Front and the political situation in Europe used for official communiques
    - 131-200 (Folder 26)
  - File 54. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Military orders, maps, intelligence reports and news summaries (Box 10.)
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 1)
    - 1-20 (Folder 2)
    - 21-50 (Folder 3)
    - 51-83 (Folder 4)
    - 84-108 (Folder 5)
    - 109-118 (Folder 6)
    - 135-189 (Folder 7)
  - File 55. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Includes eyewitness report re conditions in the Soviet Union by Gen. A. Gerua
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 8)
    - 1-55 (Folder 9)
    - 56-115 (Folder 10)
    - 116-138 (Folder 11)
    - 141-152 (Folder 12)
    - 153-199 (Folder 13)
    - 200-250 (Folder 14)
    - 252-312 (Folder 15)
    - 313-353 (Folder 16)
  - File 56. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Same as above (Box 11.)
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 1)
    - 1-30 (Folder 2)
    - 31-55 (Folder 3)
    - 56-88 (Folder 4)
    - 90-141 (Folder 5)
    - 141-203 (Folder 6)
  - File 57. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Same as above
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 7)
    - 1-40 (Folder 8)
    - 41-81 (Folder 9)
    - 82-114 (Folder 10)
  - File 58. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Includes material dealing with Petrograd, the condition of its defenses, transportation network, and public utilities
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 11)
    - 1-57 (Folder 12)
    - 58-135 (Folder 13)
  - File 59. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Includes material re recruitment of military personnel for the White Armies among Russian prisoners of war
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 14)
    - 1-42 (Folder 15)
    - 43-74 (Folder 16)
    - 75-105 (Folder 17)
    - 106-142 (Folder 18)
  - File 60. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Includes hand drawn maps depicting military situation in the Petrograd region, 1919. See also Box 24 (Folder 19-20)
  - File 61. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago (Box 12.)
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 1)
    - 1-14 (Folder 2)
    - 15-59 (Folder 3)
    - 60-99 (Folder 4)
    - 100-37 (Folder 5)
  - File 62. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Includes miscellaneous correspondence, report re creation of an armored car unit, proclamations and other propaganda of the White Army
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 6)
    - 1-40 (Folder 7)
    - 41-85 (Folder 8)
    - 86-139 (Folder 9)
    - 140-159 (Folder 10)
  - File 63. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Primarily material re maintenance of the Army of the North-West, including negotiations with the British Ministry of War (including Winston Churchill) re military supply and financial aid, contacts with the British Military Mission in Finland and the Baltics, relations with Finns and Estonians, the creation of a naval force and armored car units, the recruitment of personnel, and establishment of new units. Includes correspondence of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich, Lieut.-Gen. A. Gerua, Lieut.-Gen. Nikolai Golovin, Gen. Kondzerovskii, Gen. Dmitrii SHcherbachev
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 11)
    - 1-59 (Folder 12)
    - 60-101 (Folder 13)
    - 102-158 (Folder 14)
    - 159-212 (Folder 15)
    - 213-254 (Folder 16)
  - File 64. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Correspondence and reports re military situation on the Isthmus of Karelia and the Olenetsk Front
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 17)
    - 1-31 (Folder 18)
    - 32-97 (Folder 19)
    - 98-225 (Folder 20)
    - 226-241 (Folder 21)
  - File 65. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Miscellaneous material re the Baltic Fleet and river flotillas (Box 13., Folder 1-2)
  - File 66. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Material related to the administration of Eastern Finland (Folder 3-4)
  - File 67. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Miscellaneous correspondence routed through Arkhangel'sk (Folder 5-6)
  - File 68. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Miscellaneous material re Finland, including reports and excerpts from newspapers
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 7)
    - 1-59 (Folder 8)
    - 60-109 (Folder 9)
  - File 69. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Miscellaneous material related to the situation in Petrograd (Folder 10-11)
  - File 70. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Reports, telegrams, and correspondence re military situation on various fronts
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 12)
    - 1-45 (Folder 13)
    - 46-89 (Folder 14)
  - File 71. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Intelligence reports, orders and correspondence (Folder 15-16)
  - File 72. Shtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Personal military documents issued by the Soviet authorities
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 17)
    - 1-64 (Folder 18)
    - 65-143 (Folder 19)
  - File 73. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Intelligence reports, orders, and correspondence (Folder 20-21)
  - File 74. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Orders, telegrams and transcripts of telephone conversations
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 22)
    - 1-93 (Folder 23)
    - 94-185 (Folder 24)
  - File 75. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Intelligence reports and excerpts from newspapers (Box 14., Folder 1-2)
  - File 76. SHtab Glavnokomanduiushchago. Correspondence with Allied Missions in the Baltic region (Folder 3-4)
  - File 77. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Miscellaneous material, including reports, correspondence and leaflets, related to the Ingermanland Committee and the Ingermanland Regiment
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 5)
    - 1-55 (Folder 6)
    - 56-110 (Folder 7)
  - File 78. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Same as above and reports re Kronstadt
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 8)
    - 1-43 (Folder 9)
    - 44-100 (Folder 10)
  - File 79. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Same as above
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 11)
    - 1-19 (Folder 12)
    - 20-54 (Folder 13)
  - File 80. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence with the American Military Mission and the ARA (Folder 14-15)
  - File 81. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence and reports related to the treaty between the Government of the North-West and Estonia (Folder 16-17)
  - File 82. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence with the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Estonia
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 18)
    - 1-60 (Folder 19)
    - 61-108 (Folder 20)
    - 110-206 (Folder 21)
  - File 83. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence and reports concerning arrests and detentions (Folder 22-23)
  - File 84. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence with representatives of the French government in the Baltic (Folder 24-25)
  - File 85. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence, reports, and printed matter re attacks by Estonians on Russian military personnel and civilians, and the illegal confiscations of Russian supplies. Includes correspondence of Lieut.-Col. K. Kruzenshtern and Gen. I. Laidoner (Box 15.)
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 1)
    - 1-8 (Folder 2)
    - 9-50 (Folder 3)
    - 51-109 (Folder 4)
    - 110-155 (Folder 5)
  - File 86. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Policy statements re relations between Estonia and the Army of the North-West (Folder 6-7)
  - File 87. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Material related to military service (Folder 8-9)
  - File 88. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Material related to the Army of the North-West, including relations with the Allies and supply (Folder 10-11)
  - File 89. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence re sale of flax by the Army of the North-West (Folder 12-13)
  - File 90. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Material related to the detachment of Prince Lieven (Folder 14-15)
  - File 91. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence with the Finnish General Staff (Folder 16-17)
  - File 92. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence with the Provisional Government of Latvia (Folder 18-19)
  - File 93. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Correspondence re the government of Pskov and the Ivanov affair (Folder 20-21)
  - File 94. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Lists of ministers of the Government of the North-West and officials of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs. Includes correspondence of S. Lianozov, Col. K. Kruzenshtern, Maj.-Gen. Aleksandr Rodzianko, Gen. Nikolai IUdenich, Gen. F. Marsh
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 22)
    - 1-50 (Folder 23)
    - 51-98 (Folder 24)
    - 99-149 (Folder 25)
  - File 95. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Miscellaneous material re Vremenyi Grazhdanskii Komitet gor. Petrograda. Includes correspondence of Senator S. Ivanov (Folder 26-27)
  - File 96. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Government of the North-West. Drafts of orders for a Special Corps of the North-West (Folder 28)
  - File 97. Orders issued by the Special Corps of the North-West (subsequently the Army of the North-West) (Box 16.)
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 1)
    - 1-32 (Folder 2)
    - 33-83 (Folder 3)
    - 84-133 (Folder 4)
    - 134-201 (Folder 5)
    - 202-262 (Folder 6)
    - 263-301 (Folder 7)
    - 302-347 (Folder 8)
    - 348-368 (Folder 9)
    - 369-400 (Folder 10)
    - 401-446 (Folder 11)
    - 447-488 (Folder 12)
    - 489-519 (Folder 13)
    - 520-579 (Folder 14)
    - 580-624 (Folder 15)
    - 625-641 (Folder 16)
    - 642-684 (Folder 17)
    - 685-709 (Folder 18)
    - 710-762 (Folder 19)
  - File 98B. Orders issued by the Army of the North-West (Box 17.)
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 1)
    - 1-35 (Folder 2)
    - 36-94 (Folder 3)
    - 95-132 (Folder 4)
    - 133-164 (Folder 5)
    - 165-202 (Folder 6)
    - 203-242 (Folder 7)
    - 243-269 (Folder 8)
    - 270-292 (Folder 9)
  - File 99. Orders issued by the Army of the North-West
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 10)
    - 1-33 (Folder 11)
    - 34-60 (Folder 12)
    - 61-95 (Folder 13)
    - 96-121 (Folder 14)
    - 122-166 (Folder 15)
  - File 100. Orders issued by the Commander-in-Chief and the Minister of War of the Army of the North-West (Folder 16-18)
  - File 101. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Record book of incoming and outgoing documents (Box 18., Folder 1)
  - File 102. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Miscellaneous material re political situation in Europe. Includes correspondence with Russian Foreign Ministries
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 2)
    - 1-59 (Folder 3)
    - 60-114 (Folder 4)
    - 115-137 (Folder 5)
    - 138-177 (Folder 6)
    - 178-193 (Folder 7)
  - File 103. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Correspondence with A. Guchkov
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 8)
    - 1-38 (Folder 9)
    - 39-85 (Folder 10)
  - File 104. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Correspondence with Konstantin Gul'kevich
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 11)
    - 1-40 (Folder 12)
    - 41-78 (Folder 13)
  - File 105. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Correspondence with Gens. Aleksinskii, Kondzerovskii, Rodzianko, and SHcherbachev, as well as Count Konstantin Palen and G. Aleksinskii (Folder 14-15)
  - File 106. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Correspondence, reports, and minutes of meetings related to the Political Conference in Helsingfors, the Komitet po delam russkikh v Finliandii (A. Kartashev), external relations, domestic policy, and the financial situation of the Government of the North-West
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 16)
    - 1-40 (Folder 17)
    - 41-83 (Folder 18)
  - File 107. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Diary of events (Folder 19-20)
  - File 108. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Correspondence with Count Aleksandr Buxhoeveden (Folder 21-22)
  - File 109. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Correspondence of Col. Danilevskii, chief of the personal chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich (Folder 23-24)
  - File 110. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Intelligence reports (Box 19., Folder 1-2)
  - File 111. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Correspondence with and about Nikolai Ivanov and Maj.-Gen. S. Bulak-Balakhovich (Folder 3-4)
  - File 112. Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Diary of war operations (Folder 5)
  - File 113. Helsingfors office of the Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Includes orders of Lieut.-Gen. Gulevich and minutes of meetings of the Likvidatsionnaia Komissiia Sever-Zapadnoi Armii
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 6)
    - 1-30 (Folder 7)
    - 30-70 (Folder 8)
    - 71-118 (Folder 9)
  - File 114. Helsingfors office of the Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. List of the staff attached to the Helsingfors office (Folder 10-11)
  - File 115. Helsingfors office of the Personal Chancery of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich. Orders of the Commander-in-Chief (Folder 12-13)
  - File 116. Office of the Governor-General of the North-Western Province. Orders of the Governor-General and the Commander-in-Chief (Folder 14-15)
  - File 117. Office of Lieut.-Gen. Petr Glazenap. Includes reports and statistical charts re condition of the army and air force
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 16)
    - 1-26 (Folder 17)
    - 27-56 (Folder 18)
  - File 118. Miscellaneous unregistered papers. Includes correspondence of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich with A. Trepov, Dmitrii SHcherbachev, Sergei Sazonov, and G. Arsen'ev, mostly re foreign policy matters
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 19)
    - 1-31 (Folder 20)
    - 32-43 (Folder 21)
  - File 119. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material re supply of the Army of the North-West, 1919
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 22)
    - 1-18 (Folder 23)
    - 19-62 (Folder 24)
    - 63-111 (Folder 25)
    - 112-163 (Folder 26)
    - 164-211 (Folder 27)
  - File 120. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material re supply of the Army of the North-West, 1920 (Box 20., Folder 1-2)
  - File 121. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Same as above
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 3)
    - 1-40 (Folder 4)
    - 41-104 (Folder 5)
    - 105-153 (Folder 6)
  - File 122. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Same as above (Folder 7-8)
  - File 123. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Miscellaneous material re railroads
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 9)
    - 1-25 (Folder 10)
    - 26-74 (Folder 11)
    - 75-108 (Folder 12)
    - 109-149 (Folder 13)
    - 150-161 (Folder 14)
  - File 124. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Reports and printed matter related to foreign policy and foreign public opinion, especially in England and France, 1919
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 15)
    - 1-36 (Folder 16)
    - 37-89 (Folder 17)
    - 90-113 (Folder 18)
    - 114-181 (Folder 19)
  - File 125. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Letter from Arthur Raffalovich and the Chambre de Commerce Russe de Paris, 1920 (Folder 20)
  - File 126. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Correspondence, reports, and packing lists related to aid from the French, English, and American Red Cross, 1920
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 21)
    - 1-28 (Folder 22)
    - 29-53 (Folder 23)
    - 54-77 (Folder 24)
  - File 127. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Same as above. Includes correspondence of Boris Bakhmetev and N. L'vov, 1920 (Folder 25-26)
  - File 128. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material related to military matters. Includes correspondence with S. Sazonov, Lieut.-Gen. A. Gerua, Vasilii Maklakov, G. Lianozov, 1920 (Box 21.)
    - 1-47 (Folder 1)
    - 48-90 (Folder 2)
  - File 129. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad, 1919. Material related to travel by military personnel
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 3)
    - 1-60 (Folder 4)
    - 61-123 (Folder 5)
  - File 130. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Same as above, 1920 (Folder 6-7)
  - File 131. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material related to radio communication, 1920 (Folder 8-9)
  - File 132. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Correspondence related to transport of troops, 1920
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 10)
    - 1-43 (Folder 11)
    - 44-84 (Folder 12)
  - File 133. Intelligence reports and confidential correspondence re military situation, conditions in Petrograd, relations with Estonia, and political situation in France and England, 1919-1920
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 13)
    - 1-51 (Folder 14)
    - 52-122 (Folder 15)
    - 123-164 (Folder 16)
    - 165-233 (Folder 17)
  - File 134. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Minutes of meetings of the advisory council to V. Trotskii-Seniutovich
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 18)
    - 1-28 (Folder 19)
    - 29-119 (Folder 20)
  - File 135. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material related to the acquisition of food supplies in Sweden, 1919 (Folder 21)
  - File 136. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Telegrams, 1919 (Folder 22-23)
  - File 137. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Correspondence, reports, and orders related to the military, especially the recruitment and transport of Russian officers stranded in Europe and the award of citations and promotions for bravery in France
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 24)
    - 1-24 (Folder 25)
    - 25-62 (Folder 26)
  - File 138. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Press clippings, typed excerpts, correspondence, and news dispatches related the Russian situation presented in the foreign press. Includes draft of an article by Gen. A. Gerua, "Chto sdelali my I soiuzniki dlia pobedy," and dispatches by Agence Hébertot, 1919 (Box 22.)
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 1)
    - 1-61 (Folder 2)
    - 62-120 (Folder 3)
    - 121-195 (Folder 4)
    - 196-197 (Folder 5)
  - File 139. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Correspondence, reports, and policy statements related to negotiations between the Government of the North-West, Estonia, and the Allies, 1919 (Folder 6-7)
  - File 140. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Correspondence, reports, and protocols of meetings sent to Lieut.-Gen. Nikolai Iudenich
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 8)
    - 1-38 (Folder 9)
    - 39-70 (Folder 10)
    - 71-90 (Folder 11)
  - File 141. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Copies of documents brought by Gen. Gal'fter
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 12)
    - 1-36 (Folder 13)
    - 37-96 (Folder 14)
    - 97-207 (Folder 15)
    - 208-312 (Folder 16)
  - File 142. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Intelligence reports of the Military Representative in Denmark (Folder 17-18)
  - File 143. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Report re political situation in Denmark (Folder 19-20)
  - File 144. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material related to negotiations for credit from the United States for the purchase of surplus military supplies. Includes correspondence of Major Ray Powers (Folder 21-22)
  - File 145. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material related to the purchase of supplies from Emile Richard of Marseille, France (Folder 23-24)
  - File 146. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material related to the relay of telegrams to Gen. Iudenich through French channels and the use of French couriers by the Russian government (Folder 25-26)
  - File 147. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material re shipping (Folder 27-28)
  - File 148. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Correspondence related to the appointment of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich to his post (Folder 29-30)
  - File 149. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Material related to the steamship Olga (Box 23.)
    - Original binding cover describing material included in file (Folder 1)
    - 1-50 (Folder 2)
    - 51-94 (Folder 3)
    - 95-143 (Folder 4)
    - 144-203 (Folder 5)
    - 204-259 (Folder 6)
    - 260-298 (Folder 7)
  - File 150. Office of V. Trotskii-Seniutovich, representative of Gen. Nikolai IUdenich abroad. Same as above
    - 1-56 (Folder 8)
    - 57-118 (Folder 9)
    - 119-161 (Folder 10)
  - File 60. Oversize maps of the Petrograd front, 1919 (Box 24.)
- APPENDIX
  Original typescript, bound register made by Gen. Nikolai Golovin entitled "Podrobnaia Opis' Del Arkhiva Severo-Zapadnago Fronta Grazhdanskoi Voiny v Rossii 1919 I 1920 Godov. S Kratkim Izlozheniem Soderzhaniia Vsekh Dokumentov Imeiushchikh Istoricheskoe Znachenie"
  - Vol. I (Box 25.)
  - Vol. II